<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <!--created with Marxism-Leninism-Maoism Website RSS Generator-->
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Marxism-Leninism-Maoism News]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Marxism-Leninism-Maoism News - Original]]></description>
        <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io</link>
        <generator>Marxism-Leninism-Maoism Website RSS Generator</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 00:41:36 +08:00</lastBuildDate>
        <copyright>Copyright (C) 2024 Marxist-Leninist-Maoist.
Permission is granted to copy, distribute and/or modify this document under the terms of the GNU Free Documentation License, Version 1.3 or any later version published by the Free Software Foundation; with no Invariant Sections, no Front-Cover Texts, and no Back-Cover Texts. A copy of the license is included in the section entitled &quot;GNU Free Documentation License&quot;.</copyright>
        <language>en</language>
        <ttl>180</ttl>
        <image>
            <url>https://ciangcing14.github.io/Title.png</url>
            <title>Marxism-Leninism-Maoism News</title>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io</link>
        </image>
        <atom:link href="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/RSS/inside/ENG-rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Gaza: The famine is imminent (Nueva Democracia)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[We share the following article found in theHERALDO REDHeader Image: Palestinians meet in Gaza City to receive help. Source: Mahmoud ISSA/ReutersA part of the genocide that is being carried out in Gaza by the state of Israel, the people are suffering a starring growing rapidly. According to areportRecent, 1’1 million people, half of the population of Gaza, is experiencing “a catastrophic food insecurity”, the 5th and final phase of the Comprehensive Food Safety Classification (CPI). The entire population in Gaza, 2,23 million people are facing an acute food insecurity. The rest of the population is mostly in phase 4 of "emergency" while some areas in phase 3 "crisis."The entire population of Gaza is facing a high food insecurity. Source: IPCIn northern Gaza, the acute lack of food is exceeding the roof of what would be considered famine, and the acute malnutrition has probably exceeded the boundaries of the famine, and the deaths from starvation will soon reach the limits of the declared famine. According to an UN agent, the situation has led to more than200 people dieof starvation every day. It is reported that at least 27 children have already diedHave they diedof starvation in recent weeks. The projections of the CPI are that North of Gaza will begin to suffer famine at any time between May and now. South Gaza will begin famine in July.A Palestinian child who suffers acute malnutrition is treated in Rafah, Gaza. Source: ReutersSince October 7, 2023,hourly15 people are killed in Gaza, six of them children, 35 people are injured and 12 buildings are destroyed. In total at least 31,726 people have been killed by the state of Israel since the beginning of the current genocidal campaign. More than 73,792 people have been injured and more than 8,000 are missing, and half of homes in Gaza have been destroyed or damaged.While the imperialists act as if what happened in Gaza was some kind of natural disaster, where all they try to do is give a small help, what is happening is not a mystery. Even UN agents, dominated by Yankee imperialism, sayimplicitlythat the state of Israel are using starvation as a weapon of war.War laws, how often the imperialists regularly deny unless they serve their interests, are clearly defined and are well known to all soldiers of any army. The ruptures of these laws are considered war crimes.Article 55of the fourth convention of Geneva clearly declares that the state of Israel is responsible for the needs of the people under their occupation:“To the entire measure of its resources, the occupant power has the duty to supply the population in food and medical products; Especially you must import food, medicines and any other necessary article when the resources of the occupied territory are insufficient. ”The facts on the situation in Gaza, clearly show that the state of Israel is committing a war crime breaking this law.On January 26, the International Court of Justice (ICJ) made apreliminary statement,that said the following:“The State of Israel must, according to its obligations under the Convention on the Prevention and Punishment of the Crime of Genocide, in relation to the Palestinians in Gaza, take all the measures in their hand to avoid the commission of all acts of face to what was said in article II of this convention. "British Oxfam NGO hasdenunciatedThis despite the fact that ICJ's criteria is that Israel continues to block Gaza deliberately. Among the various methods, the state of Israel does so as follows: blocking help by creating bottlenecks only allowing help through two crosses; imposing a bureaucratic inspection system which delays trucks, on average for 20 days; and rejecting the necessary supplies such as fuel, generators, protective material and communications equipment, stating that this can only be used for military purposes.But not only neglecting to provide the employed population with the necessary supplies, also blocking other parts of doing so, the state of Israel is also eating a war crime breaching article 23 of the Fourth Convention of Geneva. This article requires states that "the free step of all shipping of medicines and health material" for civilians and "will also allow the free step of any shipment of indispensable food, clothes and tonic reserved for children of less than fifteen years and for women or parturients. "Paragraph 2 of article 70of the additional protocol for conventions expands this obligation:"2. The parties in conflict and the high contracting parts will allow and facilitate the quick and unblocking step of all shipments, materials and relief personnel provided in accordance with the provisions of this section, even in the event that such assistance is intended for the civil population of the adverse part. "Paragraph 1 of article 54 of the additional protocol I to the Geneva conventions defines the use of starvation as a gun of war, as a war crime:“1. It is prohibited, as a war method, to make civilians suffer hungry. ”Subsequently in paragraph 2 of the same article, establishes that:"2. It is prohibited to attack, destroy, subtract or use the indispensable assets for the survival of the civilian population, such as food items and agricultural areas that produce them, crops, livestock, facilities and reserves of drinking water and the works of Irrigation, with the deliberate intention of depriving of these assets, for their value as means to ensure subsistence, civil population or adverse part, whatever reason, either to make civilians suffer hungry, to provoke your displacement, or with any other purpose. "It has beeninformedthat in Gaza 83% of the wells are not operational.While they ignore the obvious war crimes committed by the state of Israel, the imperialists, acting as if it were a natural disaster, try to give the impression that they want to help the people of Gaza with insufficient measures such as air throws of material. When theseThey do not fall into the seaoPeople killAfter failing the parachutes, they are still a drop in the ocean for the Palestinian hungry. German imperialism has deployed two transport aircraft to launch help on Gaza, however these aircraft can only transport 18 tons each. This is less than the capacity of a truck, which usually has about 20 tons. While the population of Gaza needs around 500 help trucks every day, they have only entered Gaza 2,874 trucks in February, less than 100 per day. The current trend is that this amount of help is decreasing.]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T00-00-00-08-00-Nueva_Democracia.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T00-00-00-08-00-Nueva_Democracia.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/Nueva Democracia/Images/2024-03-22T00-00-00-08-00/000000.png"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PC March 21 - Meloni in Egypt: the plans of Italian imperialism and the role of Al Sisi at the service of imperialism (from counter -core Rossusoia of 20/03) (proletari comunisti)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The Mediterranean, Africa and the Middle East are the other war front lit by the interimperialist dispute, with the military troops of the ...]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T00-51-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T00-51-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 00:51:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/proletari comunisti/Images/2024-03-22T00-51-00-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[On International Day of Poetry | Workers Revolution (Revolucion Obrera)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[On the International Day of Poetry we share two poems of struggle, one from the Peruvian poet Manuel Scorza and the other of the Chilean poet Pablo Neruda.]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T01-19-35-08-00-Revolucion_Obrera.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T01-19-35-08-00-Revolucion_Obrera.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 01:19:35 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/Revolucion Obrera/Images/2024-03-22T01-19-35-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Oaxaca without water, drought or looting? (Periódico Mural)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[In recent months, more than 4,326 hectares of land were affected by terrible forest fires caused by the landowner or arising as a phenomenon of the Estío season ...]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T02-38-47-08-00-Periódico_Mural.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T02-38-47-08-00-Periódico_Mural.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 02:38:47 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/Periódico Mural/Images/2024-03-22T02-38-47-08-00/000000.png"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[New high school is approved after parliament agreement with government - the new democracy (A Nova Democracia)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Approval directly contradicted the interests of students and teachers who criticized and condemned even in important mobilizations across the country throughout the last year. Instead of a reformulation in neither, teachers and students required the total revocation of the measure.]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T03-06-19-08-00-A_Nova_Democracia.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T03-06-19-08-00-A_Nova_Democracia.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 03:06:19 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/A Nova Democracia/Images/2024-03-22T03-06-19-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[March 21 - Solidarity with the companions of Antududo affected by the repression of state - Hands down by those who fight against the masters and the government of the imperialist war (proletari comunisti)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The Palermo Police Headquarters issued three restrictive precautionary measures towards 3 militants of anturudes "A pre -trial detention in prison and ...]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T03-23-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T03-23-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 03:23:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/Title.png"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PC March 21 - Work training - The action in the class and the class position in the movements - Lenin "What to do?" (proletari comunisti)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Lenin says that to develop the political consciousness of the proletariat, the denunciation of each event must be brought to the working class ...]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T03-35-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T03-35-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 03:35:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/proletari comunisti/Images/2024-03-22T03-35-00-08-00/000000.png"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Madrid: Mobilization of the masses manages to avoid the eviction of the CPK La Bankarrota (Servir al pueblo)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The Madrid popular movement managed to avoid the eviction of the CPK (Kolelectivized political center) La Bankarrota, which was scheduled on Wednesday, March 20. The eviction was pr ...]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T03-45-13-08-00-Servir_al_pueblo.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T03-45-13-08-00-Servir_al_pueblo.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 03:45:13 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/Servir al pueblo/Images/2024-03-22T03-45-13-08-00/000000.jpeg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[NRW: School Minister Feller falls in the back of the parents (Dem Volke Dienen)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Internet platform for the development of a revolutionary movement]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T03-58-46-08-00-Dem_Volke_Dienen.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T03-58-46-08-00-Dem_Volke_Dienen.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 03:58:46 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/Title.png"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[More reports from the 8th of March – The Red Herald (Red Herald)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[We publish here further reports of actions for the 8th of March.]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T07-25-00-08-00-Red_Herald.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T07-25-00-08-00-Red_Herald.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 07:25:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/Red Herald/Images/2024-03-22T07-25-00-08-00/000000.png"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AND: Weekly editorial – Appeasement only feeds coupism – The Red Herald (Red Herald)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[When Luiz Inácio chooses the policy of appeasement to deal with the military crisis, he is allowing all favorable conditions to be reestablished for the military High Command to return to the offensive later on.]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T07-30-00-08-00-Red_Herald.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T07-30-00-08-00-Red_Herald.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 07:30:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/Red Herald/Images/2024-03-22T07-30-00-08-00/000000.png"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Snap Elections in Catalonia: Discard Illusions and Prepare for Struggle. Boycott the Electoral Farce! – The Red Herald (Red Herald)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The President of the Generality, Pere Aragonès, announced last Wednesday, March 13, that the regional elections were expedited to May 12.]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T07-34-00-08-00-Red_Herald.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T07-34-00-08-00-Red_Herald.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 07:34:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/Red Herald/Images/2024-03-22T07-34-00-08-00/000000.png"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Peasants are repressed by agents of the Federal Police and paramilitary in Machadinho d'Oeste, Rondônia - The New Democracy (A Nova Democracia)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Peasants who recently occupied Fazenda Ipê, in Machadinho d'Oeste, northeast of Rondônia, denounced a brutal attack on camp, promoted by a bunch of PF paramilitar and police officers on March 7, 2024.]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T07-36-28-08-00-A_Nova_Democracia.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T07-36-28-08-00-A_Nova_Democracia.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 07:36:28 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/A Nova Democracia/Images/2024-03-22T07-36-28-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PALO QUEMADO-LAS PAMPAS RESISTS MINING IMPERIALISM (FDLP EC)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Imperialism displays its claws the imperialist boots, of different lysa, invade Ecuador, in search of our land, recurs ...]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T11-53-00-08-00-FDLP_EC.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T11-53-00-08-00-FDLP_EC.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 11:53:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/FDLP EC/Images/2024-03-22T11-53-00-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Brazil: The People's Court Against Earth Terms and Land -based Crimes held in Junco Do Maranhão (Socialistisk Revolution)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Hereby we publish an unofficial translation of an article published in A Nova Democracia (And). On March 9 and 10, the victorious People's Court against landscapes and land -based crimes… became]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T12-00-00-08-00-Socialistisk_Revolution.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T12-00-00-08-00-Socialistisk_Revolution.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 12:00:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/Socialistisk Revolution/Images/2024-03-22T12-00-00-08-00/000000.png"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From Ang Bayan: Wage Armed Struggle Against The  US-Marcos Regime’s Fascist Onslaught - Redspark (Redspark)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Ang Bayan March 21, 2024 The Filipino people are burning with rage at the US-Marcos regime over its all-out fascist]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T13-00-51-08-00-Redspark.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T13-00-51-08-00-Redspark.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 13:00:51 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/Redspark/Images/2024-03-22T13-00-51-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PC March 22 - Maximum support for the decision of the University of Turin for the blocking of collaboration with Israel - Info (proletari comunisti)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[War in Gaza, the University of Turin blocks the call for collaboration with Israel. Meloni: "Relating choice" The University is the first to So ...]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T14-44-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T14-44-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 14:44:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/Title.png"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PC 22 March - Writings and interventions on the Municipality of Paris based on the discourse of communist proletarians on the occasion of the anniversary of 18 March - 1 (proletari comunisti)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA["His true secret was this: that it was essentially a government class government ... ... the product of the class fight of the Prod ...]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T14-52-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T14-52-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 14:52:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/Title.png"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[In freedom with charges the ten solidarity activists with Palestine detained in Barcelona - New Manifestation Madrid - Solidarity Info (maoistroad)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[/ By writing Kaosenlared the arrests are related to facts ...]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T15-12-00-08-00-maoistroad.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T15-12-00-08-00-maoistroad.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 15:12:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/maoistroad/Images/2024-03-22T15-12-00-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[France: attack on a police station following the death of a young man killed by a collision with a police vehicle (maoistroad)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Several dozen people targeted the Courneuve police station (Seine-Saint-Denis) Sunday evening, proceeding ...]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T15-14-00-08-00-maoistroad.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T15-14-00-08-00-maoistroad.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 15:14:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/maoistroad/Images/2024-03-22T15-14-00-08-00/000000.png"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Rearmament plans for the german military  - info (maoistroad)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Rearmament plans for the german military					  							  					 	 	 		 						    	    	    			  		 Ready for war." This is what ...]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T15-14-00-08-00-z000002-maoistroad.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T15-14-00-08-00-z000002-maoistroad.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 15:14:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/maoistroad/Images/2024-03-22T15-14-00-08-00-z000002/000000.jpeg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CPI (Maoist) CC Calls Upon Masses To Celebrate March 23rd As Anti-Imperialism Day - info - (maoistroad)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[tomorrow ICSPWI publishes the call          Hyderabad District, March 21, 2024: The Central  Committee of the CPI (Maoist) has called upon...]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T15-22-00-08-00-maoistroad.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T15-22-00-08-00-maoistroad.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 15:22:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/maoistroad/Images/2024-03-22T15-22-00-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Assembly for Ilaria Salis in Turin (femminismo proletario rivoluzionario)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[You can follow Facebook live]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T17-00-00-08-00-femminismo_proletario_rivoluzionario.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T17-00-00-08-00-femminismo_proletario_rivoluzionario.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 17:00:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/femminismo proletario rivoluzionario/Images/2024-03-22T17-00-00-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[EU and NATO upgrade: Austria participates. (DIE ROTE FAHNE)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[NATO Secretary General Jens Stoltenberg recently demanded the changeover to war economy, in the EU the nuclear armament of the Union and Austria undertook to pay 1.17 billion annually to Ukraine. These are just the top of the current military advances that are supposed to drive the war course. Regardless of neutrality, the Austrian population is drawn into the war plans of the rulers. How can this be countered? Austrian]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T17-03-12-08-00-DIE_ROTE_FAHNE.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T17-03-12-08-00-DIE_ROTE_FAHNE.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 17:03:12 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/DIE ROTE FAHNE/Images/2024-03-22T17-03-12-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Holded neutrality? Restore neutrality! (DIE ROTE FAHNE)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[After a first advance for the official elimination of neutrality was dropped relatively quickly about two years ago, the complete hollowing out neutrality has been practiced in rapid steps since then. In words, politicians of various strings defend neutrality, while in deeds they rarely pay attention. The restoration of neutrality becomes the demand for those who face these developments - and that is many! In February this year]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T17-20-18-08-00-DIE_ROTE_FAHNE.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T17-20-18-08-00-DIE_ROTE_FAHNE.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 17:20:18 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/DIE ROTE FAHNE/Images/2024-03-22T17-20-18-08-00/000000.png"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[THESSALONIKI Mass CONCEPTING AND Fighter Demonstration of the Palestinian People's Genocide (Resistance in the neighbourhood)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T17-43-00-08-00-Resistance_in_the_neighbourhood.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T17-43-00-08-00-Resistance_in_the_neighbourhood.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 17:43:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/Resistance in the neighbourhood/Images/2024-03-22T17-43-00-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A tribute to Tina Modotti, a great woman from the 20s, an important political activist to whom the national gallery Jeu de Peume in Paris dedicated a beautiful exhibition (femminismo proletario rivoluzionario)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Tina Modotti, the eye of the Revolution in Paris, the Jeu de Paume National Gallery until 12/05/2024 pays homage to Tina Modotti (1896 -...]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T17-46-00-08-00-femminismo_proletario_rivoluzionario.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T17-46-00-08-00-femminismo_proletario_rivoluzionario.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 17:46:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/femminismo proletario rivoluzionario/Images/2024-03-22T17-46-00-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[From Ang Bayan: Women Bear Half The Imperialist Sky - Redspark (Redspark)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Ang Bayan March 21, 2024 Filipino women bear the worst effects of the neo-liberal policies imposed by US imperialism and]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T18-00-20-08-00-Redspark.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T18-00-20-08-00-Redspark.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 18:00:20 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/Redspark/Images/2024-03-22T18-00-20-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No. 28 of the red flag (DIE ROTE FAHNE)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Dear readers, the No. 28 of the Red flag is now available in the online and print version. The subscription is here: 
 Editorial: For some current questions. Beating article: EU and NATO prepare on: Austria participates. No. 28 | March 2024]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T18-45-49-08-00-DIE_ROTE_FAHNE.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T18-45-49-08-00-DIE_ROTE_FAHNE.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 18:45:49 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/DIE ROTE FAHNE/Images/2024-03-22T18-45-49-08-00/000000.png"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PC 22 March - 12 noon counter -information Rosso Opera - Palermo: against war and repression / from Fincantieri / workers speak (proletari comunisti)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T19-00-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T19-00-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 19:00:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/proletari comunisti/Images/2024-03-22T19-00-00-08-00/000000.png"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PC 22 March - Support for the Palestinian people and to their resistance must continue (as a counter -information Rossusoia of 21/03) (proletari comunisti)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[We want to put some aspects in the center behind the mobilization for Palestine that developed in our country and that r ...]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T19-00-00-08-00-z000002-proletari_comunisti.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T19-00-00-08-00-z000002-proletari_comunisti.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 19:00:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/proletari comunisti/Images/2024-03-22T19-00-00-08-00-z000002/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[STUDENT RESISTANCE Strict measures for the absences and penalties for students! Terrorism will not pass! (Resistance in the neighbourhood)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T19-56-00-08-00-Resistance_in_the_neighbourhood.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T19-56-00-08-00-Resistance_in_the_neighbourhood.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 19:56:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/Resistance in the neighbourhood/Images/2024-03-22T19-56-00-08-00/000000.jpeg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fight of two lines No. 3 in Spanish | Workers Revolution (Revolucion Obrera)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Comrades of the International Communist Movement, we announce the Magazine Lucha de Two Lines No. 3, which is a special delivery on the occasion of the]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T20-00-00-08-00-Revolucion_Obrera.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T20-00-00-08-00-Revolucion_Obrera.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 20:00:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/Revolucion Obrera/Images/2024-03-22T20-00-00-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PC March 22 - Rossusoia and working training counter -information: necessary tools for the action of the Communists today (from counter -information Rossusoia of 03/21) (proletari comunisti)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[For the debate between the companions, in the workers' avant -garde, in the movement for the construction of the Communist Party the economic press of the ...]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T20-00-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T20-00-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 20:00:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/proletari comunisti/Images/2024-03-22T20-00-00-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[TV -N Saxony - heated mood (Dem Volke Dienen)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Internet platform for the development of a revolutionary movement]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T20-24-30-08-00-Dem_Volke_Dienen.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T20-24-30-08-00-Dem_Volke_Dienen.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 20:24:30 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/Dem Volke Dienen/Images/2024-03-22T20-24-30-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bergen: activists blocked Equinor for Palestine (Tjen Folket)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Earn Folket Media was present at a demonstration outside Equinor's office at Sandsli in Bergen. Protesters blocked the driveway to the office's parking lot. It was a collaboration between…]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T22-49-44-08-00-Tjen_Folket.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T22-49-44-08-00-Tjen_Folket.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 22:49:44 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/Tjen Folket/Images/2024-03-22T22-49-44-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Current situation: Notes on the World Crisis (9. Declarations on Ukraine) (Association New Democracy)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[On the latest statements of the imperialist representatives in this post, we recorded some of the latest statements of ...]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T22-54-00-08-00-Association_New_Democracy.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-22T22-54-00-08-00-Association_New_Democracy.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 22:54:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/Association New Democracy/Images/2024-03-22T22-54-00-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Active tugboat between the US and Israel while the slaughter continues - KKE (M -L) (KKE m l)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[We have now entered the sixth month of the Genocystic slaughter of the Zionist state of Israel against the people of Palestine in the Gaza Strip. The unstoppable daily bombings turn the area into ruins full of murdered civilians, while the Israeli war council was approved and the invasion of Rafa.]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T00-00-00-08-00-KKE_m_l.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T00-00-00-08-00-KKE_m_l.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/KKE m l/Images/2024-03-23T00-00-00-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[To give way through the mass struggle! - KKE (M-L) (KKE m l)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[European Council President Charles Michelle proclaims that "if he wants peace, Europe needs to be prepared for war" and that we need to "go into war economy" while at the same time, the long -haired delusions and lies for lies for lies. The "Europe of the Peoples" are re -employed by the rulers to drag their peoples to the upcoming electoral farce.]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T00-00-00-08-00-z000002-KKE_m_l.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T00-00-00-08-00-z000002-KKE_m_l.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/KKE m l/Images/2024-03-23T00-00-00-08-00-z000002/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The culprits continue the concealment business - KKE (M -L) (KKE m l)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[On the issue of Tempi, the government wants to achieve two, conflicting, goals: to conceal the crime, but also to calm the anger of both relatives and people. And the pie and the dog grass, that is.]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T00-00-00-08-00-z000003-KKE_m_l.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T00-00-00-08-00-z000003-KKE_m_l.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/KKE m l/Images/2024-03-23T00-00-00-08-00-z000003/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Medicine for all the disease ... the people pay the marble - KKE (M -L) (KKE m l)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The continuity and intensity of policy that will ruin labor rights for health care and the right of the people to free and equal to all care is a given. What we should constantly concern to us is how to build resistance on the part of the popular forces in the direction of getting a barrier to this policy.]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T00-00-00-08-00-z000004-KKE_m_l.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T00-00-00-08-00-z000004-KKE_m_l.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/KKE m l/Images/2024-03-23T00-00-00-08-00-z000004/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Outside Greece from the EU! - From the European elections! - KKE (M-L) (KKE m l)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[From its initial phase and throughout its journey to its present form, the EU has been and exists as a venture of Europe's imperialists. It is a coalition to serve and promote interests and aspirations before all its imperialist pillars.]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T00-00-00-08-00-z000005-KKE_m_l.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T00-00-00-08-00-z000005-KKE_m_l.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/KKE m l/Images/2024-03-23T00-00-00-08-00-z000005/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How many certifications make a high school graduate? - KKE (M-L) (KKE m l)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Students' resistance in order not to pass the new measures and to overthrow all anti -populist laws in education is a necessity. Through their 5 -member and 15 -member trade unions, with weapons of general assemblies, occupations and demonstrations, they must make decisions to continue the fight!]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T00-00-00-08-00-z000006-KKE_m_l.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T00-00-00-08-00-z000006-KKE_m_l.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/KKE m l/Images/2024-03-23T00-00-00-08-00-z000006/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The intensity of repression cannot "persuade" the youth to submit - KKE (M -L) (KKE m l)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The invasion of Police Forces at the Aristotle University of Thessaloniki at the Aristotle University of Thessaloniki at noon on Saturday 16/3 to evacuate the occupations that were held in sections and the arrest of 49 students is a serious example of the system's revanchism.]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T00-00-00-08-00-z000007-KKE_m_l.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T00-00-00-08-00-z000007-KKE_m_l.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/KKE m l/Images/2024-03-23T00-00-00-08-00-z000007/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Kiev in despair, Europe in confusion, Putin… reinforced - KKE (M -L) (KKE m l)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Ukraine's possible defeat will highlight the weaknesses of Western mechanisms. And this is something that exacerbates a sense of strategic impasse, especially for European imperialists.]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T00-00-00-08-00-z000008-KKE_m_l.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T00-00-00-08-00-z000008-KKE_m_l.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/KKE m l/Images/2024-03-23T00-00-00-08-00-z000008/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PC 22 March - 23 March 1944 - 23 March 2024: 80 years from the heroic action of the gap in via Rasella (proletari comunisti)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[After the fall of the fascist regime and the formation of the Badoglio government in Rome some divisions of the Royal Army had merged: the 8th set ...]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T00-38-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T00-38-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 00:38:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/proletari comunisti/Images/2024-03-23T00-38-00-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PC March 22 - exploited migrants - Al Jazeera is right ... while the Italian press often is silent (proletari comunisti)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Al Jazeera's investigation: "Migrants exploited and mistreated in the lands of Barolo and Barbaresco" in the investigation is told, among others, ...]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T00-43-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T00-43-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 00:43:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/Title.png"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PC 22 March - Initiatives for Palestine (proletari comunisti)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T00-54-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T00-54-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 00:54:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/proletari comunisti/Images/2024-03-23T00-54-00-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Celebrate historic 23rd March as Anti-Imperialist Day in the immortal revolutionaries' memories of Comrades Bhagat Singh, Sukdev, and Rajguru. _  Communist Party of India (Maoist) (maoistroad)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Let us defeat Imperialism. Let us smash Brahmanical Hindutva Fascism. Let us continue our struggle to fulfill the dreams of all great martyr...]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T01-07-00-08-00-maoistroad.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T01-07-00-08-00-maoistroad.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 01:07:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/Title.png"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Journal of two Lines No. 3 in Spanish finally came out! (maoistroad)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T01-14-00-08-00-maoistroad.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T01-14-00-08-00-maoistroad.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 01:14:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/maoistroad/Images/2024-03-23T01-14-00-08-00/000000.png"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CDMX Actions by Dr. SERNAS GARCÍA (Association New Democracy)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Our colleagues in Mexico City have carried out some actions in demand for life of Dr. Ernesto Sernas ...]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T01-27-00-08-00-Association_New_Democracy.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T01-27-00-08-00-Association_New_Democracy.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 01:27:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/Association New Democracy/Images/2024-03-23T01-27-00-08-00/000000.jpeg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PC 22 March - Bologna. Students uploaded by the police, ... by now the Meloni/Salvini/Planted government has declared war on the students who protest (proletari comunisti)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[They contested Minister Bernini and the agreements between University and Israel in the central Via Indipendenza of Bologna the ...]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T01-46-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T01-46-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 01:46:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/proletari comunisti/Images/2024-03-23T01-46-00-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[On the occasion of the 25th anniversary of NATO bombings - the 1997 Party of Work Party - Party of Labor (PARTIJA RADA)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[NATO troops, together with their political staffs are on the territory of Yugoslavia, distributed in BiH, Croatia and Macedonia. The NATO Pact created American imperialists in cooperation with the Imperialists of Western Europe in 1947. Concerned about the great victories of the Soviet Union, the creation of the Socialist Tabor, the victory of the Red Army in China and the more powerful anticolonial and anti-primerial movement in]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T01-46-57-08-00-PARTIJA_RADA.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T01-46-57-08-00-PARTIJA_RADA.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 01:46:57 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/PARTIJA RADA/Images/2024-03-23T01-46-57-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[One more sample of the need to conquer class independence in the trade union movement | Workers Revolution (Revolucion Obrera)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Meanwhile, the CUT Congress did give him a decision and by delegates, with the aggravating man who arrived the documents already made and machine]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T02-00-00-08-00-Revolucion_Obrera.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T02-00-00-08-00-Revolucion_Obrera.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 02:00:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/Revolucion Obrera/Images/2024-03-23T02-00-00-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No more war against the indigenous people | Workers Revolution (Revolucion Obrera)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Since Saturday, March 16, several acts of violence against the NASA community have been presented in the rural area of the municipality of Toribío (Cauca), there it was]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T02-00-45-08-00-Revolucion_Obrera.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T02-00-45-08-00-Revolucion_Obrera.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 02:00:45 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/Revolucion Obrera/Images/2024-03-23T02-00-45-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[STF Minister orders Mauro Cid's arrest after leakage of audios; Bolsonaro's defense celebrates - The New Democracy (A Nova Democracia)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Supreme Federal Court Minister Alexandre de Moraes ordered, on the afternoon of March 22, the pre-trial detention of Army Lieutenant Colonel Mauro, Mauro]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T03-40-20-08-00-A_Nova_Democracia.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T03-40-20-08-00-A_Nova_Democracia.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 03:40:20 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/A Nova Democracia/Images/2024-03-23T03-40-20-08-00/000000.png"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Former commander and Luiz Inacio prevented arrest of 'green chickens' on 8/1 to protect family from General Villas-Bôas-The New Democracy (A Nova Democracia)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The decision was accepted by Luiz Inácio, who prevarized with Arruda in the face of possibilities, real or not, of "subline".]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T04-16-53-08-00-A_Nova_Democracia.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T04-16-53-08-00-A_Nova_Democracia.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 04:16:53 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/A Nova Democracia/Images/2024-03-23T04-16-53-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[RJ: Manifestation requires end of lawsuit against motorcycle taxi drivers unfairly accused (see video) - the new democracy (A Nova Democracia)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[On March 20, a demonstration required the end of the lawsuit against Diego Felipe, motorcycle taxi driver and maqueiro at the UFRJ Hospital. He is accused by the PM of transporting a dismantled rifle, which was with a passenger transported by the worker.]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T06-59-23-08-00-A_Nova_Democracia.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T06-59-23-08-00-A_Nova_Democracia.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 06:59:23 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/A Nova Democracia/Images/2024-03-23T06-59-23-08-00/000000.jpeg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Brazil: The 23 persecuted activists from 2013/14 were acquitted – The Red Herald (Red Herald)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[A Nova Democracia reports that on Tuesday, March 19, the trial of the request for acquittal of the 23 political activists persecuted for their participation in the 2013 and 2014 demonstrations took place at the Court in Rio de Janeiro.]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T07-50-00-08-00-Red_Herald.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T07-50-00-08-00-Red_Herald.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 07:50:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/Red Herald/Images/2024-03-23T07-50-00-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Nigeria: The Wrath of the Masses – The Red Herald (Red Herald)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[On Thursday, last week, a dispute on land between people from Okuama, Ughelli South, and Okoloba, Bomadi, in Nigeria's southern state of Delta, took place. The armed forces of the old State tried to intervene but received what they did not expect.]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T07-56-00-08-00-Red_Herald.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T07-56-00-08-00-Red_Herald.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 07:56:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/Red Herald/Images/2024-03-23T07-56-00-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[War-torn Sudan heading for disaster – The Red Herald (Red Herald)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[We have previously reported on the war in Sudan portraying an initial analysis of the circumstances of the outbreak of the war.]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T07-59-00-08-00-Red_Herald.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T07-59-00-08-00-Red_Herald.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 07:59:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/Red Herald/Images/2024-03-23T07-59-00-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Again short -time work ... (DIE ROTE FAHNE)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[(Correspondence from the company) At the end of December, we received the announcement that the company leave is extended due to the poor order situation and that short-time work will be registered again in 2024. at the expense of the workers! Now we should be registered for a year for short -time work, which means that we are now getting ten percent less wages.]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T08-09-05-08-00-DIE_ROTE_FAHNE.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T08-09-05-08-00-DIE_ROTE_FAHNE.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 08:09:05 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/DIE ROTE FAHNE/Images/2024-03-23T08-09-05-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PIRAEUS From the demonstration against trade union-political persecutions at the Piraeus Municipal Theater (Resistance in the neighbourhood)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T10-33-00-08-00-Resistance_in_the_neighbourhood.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T10-33-00-08-00-Resistance_in_the_neighbourhood.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 10:33:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/Resistance in the neighbourhood/Images/2024-03-23T10-33-00-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Heraklion By gathering a complaint of political-syndicate persecutions (Resistance in the neighbourhood)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T10-33-00-08-00-z000002-Resistance_in_the_neighbourhood.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T10-33-00-08-00-z000002-Resistance_in_the_neighbourhood.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 10:33:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/Resistance in the neighbourhood/Images/2024-03-23T10-33-00-08-00-z000002/000000.png"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Do you have to celebrate on March 20? (Resistance in the neighbourhood)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T10-33-00-08-00-z000003-Resistance_in_the_neighbourhood.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T10-33-00-08-00-z000003-Resistance_in_the_neighbourhood.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 10:33:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/Resistance in the neighbourhood/Images/2024-03-23T10-33-00-08-00-z000003/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PROGRITION FLAGE Saturday 23 March 2024 • Φ.959 | With (euro) illusions they want to control social anger! To give way through the mass struggle! (Resistance in the neighbourhood)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T10-49-00-08-00-Resistance_in_the_neighbourhood.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T10-49-00-08-00-Resistance_in_the_neighbourhood.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 10:49:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/Resistance in the neighbourhood/Images/2024-03-23T10-49-00-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Parties Involved Decide To Continue With Socialist Front Of Nepal - Redspark (Redspark)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Kathmandu, March 22, 2024: The parties concerned have agreed to continue the four-party Socialist Front of Nepal. Top leaders of]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T13-00-19-08-00-Redspark.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T13-00-19-08-00-Redspark.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 13:00:19 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/Redspark/Images/2024-03-23T13-00-19-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PC 23 March - Taranto Today event: Palestine/against imperialism (proletari comunisti)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T14-26-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T14-26-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 14:26:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/proletari comunisti/Images/2024-03-23T14-26-00-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Egypt - Workers' strikes: Mahalla al Kubra's workers on the pitch again (femminismo proletario rivoluzionario)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[As we have already denounced (*), the Egyptian regime of Al Sisi is making a fence in the Sinai desert to lock up the PAL ...]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T14-32-00-08-00-femminismo_proletario_rivoluzionario.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T14-32-00-08-00-femminismo_proletario_rivoluzionario.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 14:32:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/femminismo proletario rivoluzionario/Images/2024-03-23T14-32-00-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PC 23 March - Newroz ... RESISTAIN RESISTANCE - An intervention of the Turkish companions (proletari comunisti)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[in via di traduzione  Description No: 2024/2   Revolt, Resistance, Uprising against Annihilation, Denial and Assimilation; Occupation and An...]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T16-21-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T16-21-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 16:21:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/proletari comunisti/Images/2024-03-23T16-21-00-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PC 23 March - Writings and interventions on the Municipality of Paris based on the discourse of communist proletarians on the occasion of the anniversary of 18 March - 2 (proletari comunisti)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Mao and the Municipality of Paris da Mao Works is of extreme importance for the revolutionary people to have the rifle in hand the historical experience of ...]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T16-22-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T16-22-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 16:22:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/proletari comunisti/Images/2024-03-23T16-22-00-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[A report on the Assembly for Ilaria Salis in Turin - by a lawyer of the MFPR of Taranto (femminismo proletario rivoluzionario)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[On March 28 in Budapest, the second hearing will be celebrated which sees Ilaria Salis attributed in a trial whose value is only political ....]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T16-27-00-08-00-femminismo_proletario_rivoluzionario.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T16-27-00-08-00-femminismo_proletario_rivoluzionario.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 16:27:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/femminismo proletario rivoluzionario/Images/2024-03-23T16-27-00-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PC March 23 - A report on the Assembly for Ilaria Salis in Turin - by a lawyer of the MFPR of Taranto (proletari comunisti)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[On March 28 in Budapest, the second hearing will be celebrated which sees Ilaria Salis attributed in a trial whose value is only politicians ...]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T16-31-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T16-31-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 16:31:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/proletari comunisti/Images/2024-03-23T16-31-00-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PC March 23 - India - March 23 Antimperialist day in memory of revolutionary martyrs (proletari comunisti)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Communist Party of India (Maoista) Central Regional Office 20 March 2022 We celebrate the historian March 23 as already ...]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T17-18-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T17-18-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 17:18:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/proletari comunisti/Images/2024-03-23T17-18-00-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[CPI (Maoist) CC Calls Upon Masses To Celebrate March 23rd As Anti-Imperialism Day – info (ICSPW India)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Hyderabad District, March 21, 2024: The Central Committee of the CPI (Maoist) has called upon all democratic forces and others including peasantry, Dalits, women’s organizations, and others to…]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T17-48-10-08-00-ICSPW_India.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T17-48-10-08-00-ICSPW_India.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 17:48:10 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/ICSPW India/Images/2024-03-23T17-48-10-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Celebrate historic 23rd March as Anti-Imperialist Day in the immortal revolutionaries’ memories of Comrades Bhagat Singh, Sukdev, and Rajguru. _ Communist Party of India (Maoist) (ICSPW India)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Let us defeat Imperialism. Let us smash Brahmanical Hindutva Fascism.Let us continue our struggle to fulfill the dreams of all great martyrs of freedom movement and let us fight for a New Democratic…]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T17-52-17-08-00-ICSPW_India.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T17-52-17-08-00-ICSPW_India.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 17:52:17 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/Title.png"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Hamburg: event on the occasion of March 18 (Dem Volke Dienen)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Internet platform for the development of a revolutionary movement]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T18-00-00-08-00-Dem_Volke_Dienen.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T18-00-00-08-00-Dem_Volke_Dienen.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 18:00:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/Dem Volke Dienen/Images/2024-03-23T18-00-00-08-00/000000.png"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[UML Chairman Oli Denies Speculations Of His Party's Inclusion In Socialist Front Of Nepal - Redspark (Redspark)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Kathmandu, March 22, 2024: KP Sharma Oli, Chairman of the CPN-UML, has dismissed speculations regarding his party’s potential entry into]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T18-00-49-08-00-Redspark.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T18-00-49-08-00-Redspark.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 18:00:49 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/Redspark/Images/2024-03-23T18-00-49-08-00/000000.png"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PC March 23 - Against war, against death factories: Liber* tutt*. Procession today in Palermo (proletari comunisti)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[From Piazza Bellini 4pm, 30 - Palermo precautionary measures for three anthudium militants for a sanction to Leonardo S.p.A. Repression ...]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T18-40-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T18-40-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 18:40:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/proletari comunisti/Images/2024-03-23T18-40-00-08-00/000000.png"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PC March 23 - Milan, Pro Palestine demonstrators invade the market in Piazza Portello. An avant -garde initiative that goes in the right direction and necessary to extend and continue (proletari comunisti)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Article and video of the Sole24ore https: //stream24.ilsole24ore.com/video/italia/milano-corto-contro- company- accusata- export-a israle ...]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T19-01-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T19-01-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 19:01:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/proletari comunisti/Images/2024-03-23T19-01-00-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Crimes of Israel – The Red Herald (Red Herald)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[In the International Military Tribunal, know as the Nuremberg trial, the Soviet Union together with Yankee, British and French imperialism tried crimes of the European Axis, mainly by the Nazis.]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T19-55-00-08-00-Red_Herald.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T19-55-00-08-00-Red_Herald.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 19:55:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/Red Herald/Images/2024-03-23T19-55-00-08-00/000000.png"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Denmark: The “IUD Campaign” and the social engineering of Danish colonialism in Greenland – The Red Herald (Red Herald)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Thousands of Greenlandic women were involuntarily implanted with IUDs to prevent them from becoming pregnant in the 1960s-1970s by the Danish colonial authorities. This was done to reduce population growth in Greenland - a cruel and cynical expression of population control as part of Danish imperialism's colonial policy in Greenland.]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T20-03-00-08-00-Red_Herald.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T20-03-00-08-00-Red_Herald.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 20:03:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/Red Herald/Images/2024-03-23T20-03-00-08-00/000000.png"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[US to build “all-encompassing” spy satellite network – The Red Herald (Red Herald)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[SpaceX is building network of spy satellites called ”Starshield” under a classified contract with the US government. SpaceX has a $1.8 billion contract with the National Reconnaissance Office (NRO), which includes personnel from the CIA and the Space Forces, to build a network of satellites able to quickly single out military targets almost anywhere in the world to support the ground forces of US imperialism.]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T20-12-00-08-00-Red_Herald.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T20-12-00-08-00-Red_Herald.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 20:12:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/Red Herald/Images/2024-03-23T20-12-00-08-00/000000.png"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The peasants took the water sources back from a large farm after hitting the gunmen in a clash (Uusi Brasilia)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Approximately 100 farmers organized by the Poor Peasant Association Jaqueira (Pernambuco) from various communities took back their water source, which had been fenced by a large farmer company. 18.…]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T21-29-59-08-00-Uusi_Brasilia.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T21-29-59-08-00-Uusi_Brasilia.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 21:29:59 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/Uusi Brasilia/Images/2024-03-23T21-29-59-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[MA: Residents of the São Benedito community in Maranhão report land grabbing crimes - the new democracy (A Nova Democracia)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The community has over 200 years of existence, with lands passed from generation to generation, in which residents work in the fields for their subsistence.]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T23-01-50-08-00-A_Nova_Democracia.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T23-01-50-08-00-A_Nova_Democracia.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 23:01:50 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/A Nova Democracia/Images/2024-03-23T23-01-50-08-00/000000.png"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PC March 23 - Egypt - Workers' strikes: Mahalla al Kubra's workers again on the field (proletari comunisti)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[As we have already denounced (*), the Egyptian regime of Al Sisi is making a fence in the Sinai desert for Straight ...]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T23-15-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-23T23-15-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2024 23:15:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-23/ORI/proletari comunisti/Images/2024-03-23T23-15-00-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
