<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <!--created with Marxism-Leninism-Maoism Website RSS Generator-->
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Marxism-Leninism-Maoism News]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Marxism-Leninism-Maoism News - Original]]></description>
        <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io</link>
        <generator>Marxism-Leninism-Maoism Website RSS Generator</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 06:56:24 +08:00</lastBuildDate>
        <copyright>Copyright (C) 2024 Marxist-Leninist-Maoist.
Permission is granted to copy, distribute and/or modify this document under the terms of the GNU Free Documentation License, Version 1.3 or any later version published by the Free Software Foundation; with no Invariant Sections, no Front-Cover Texts, and no Back-Cover Texts. A copy of the license is included in the section entitled &quot;GNU Free Documentation License&quot;.</copyright>
        <language>en</language>
        <ttl>180</ttl>
        <image>
            <url>https://ciangcing14.github.io/Title.png</url>
            <title>Marxism-Leninism-Maoism News</title>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io</link>
        </image>
        <atom:link href="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/RSS/inside/ENG-rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The fines for possession of the KKE (M-L) were canceled by the Municipality of Athens-KKE (M-L) (KKE m l)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The cancellation of fines for possessions, which had imposed on the KKE (M-L) during the June 2023 parliamentary elections, was announced by the municipality of Athens, in a relevant document, on the grounds of "Antimony".]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T00-00-00-08-00-KKE_m_l.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T00-00-00-08-00-KKE_m_l.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ORI/KKE m l/Images/2024-03-27T00-00-00-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[It reaffirmed throughout the country. They are 30,000! (Partido Comunista Revolucionario)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Memory, truth and justice was one of the slogans that toured the country reaffirming that there are 30,000! and that it was a genocide orchestrated by state terrorism. In each provincial and cities capital, human rights organizations, trade union, social, political, women and diversities, cultural groups called for marches and acts ...]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T00-00-00-08-00-Partido_Comunista_Revolucionario.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T00-00-00-08-00-Partido_Comunista_Revolucionario.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ORI/Partido Comunista Revolucionario/Images/2024-03-27T00-00-00-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Spanish state turns back in the prohibition of Telegram (Servir al pueblo)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[On March 23, the news was known that a judge of the National Court, the court that has jurisdiction throughout the state, ordered the complete closure of Telegram in the country to Caus…]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T00-03-13-08-00-Servir_al_pueblo.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T00-03-13-08-00-Servir_al_pueblo.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 00:03:13 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ORI/Servir al pueblo/Images/2024-03-27T00-03-13-08-00/000000.png"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bolsonaro's visit to the Hungary embassy reveals an international articulation of the far right - the new democracy (A Nova Democracia)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Former President Jair Bolsonaro spent two nights at Hungary diplomatic headquarters at an apparent political asylum request. This occurred four days after Jair Bolsonaro was forced to deliver his passport during Operation Tempus Veritatis.]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T02-38-11-08-00-A_Nova_Democracia.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T02-38-11-08-00-A_Nova_Democracia.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 02:38:11 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ORI/A Nova Democracia/Images/2024-03-27T02-38-11-08-00/000000.png"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[After more than a year by power: the SVM government is in crisis (Socialistisk Revolution)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[After just over a year of the SVM government, the political situation in Denmark has changed drastically. The government was planned and established at the end of 2022 after it became clear to Bourgeoi…]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T02-56-54-08-00-Socialistisk_Revolution.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T02-56-54-08-00-Socialistisk_Revolution.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 02:56:54 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/Title.png"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Putin regime seeks to deepen internal repression after attack by the Islamic State - the new democracy (A Nova Democracia)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Despite attempts by Russian State Officers of announcing the issue for their own purposes, Russian imperialism has a long history of invasions to Arab countries or of a Muslim majority.]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T03-24-48-08-00-A_Nova_Democracia.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T03-24-48-08-00-A_Nova_Democracia.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 03:24:48 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ORI/A Nova Democracia/Images/2024-03-27T03-24-48-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PB: Peasant Leadership is found murdered - the new democracy (A Nova Democracia)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The notorious murder of the organizer of the peasant camp occurs in a scenario of increased crimes of landowners and gun against peasants in struggle for the land.]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T03-37-36-08-00-A_Nova_Democracia.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T03-37-36-08-00-A_Nova_Democracia.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 03:37:36 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ORI/A Nova Democracia/Images/2024-03-27T03-37-36-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[AM: Delegate, Civil Police and PM investigators are arrested for acting in a paramilitary group - the new democracy (A Nova Democracia)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Paramilitaries kidnapped and tortured associated with drug trafficking to steal narcotics and sell to other groups.]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T03-45-39-08-00-A_Nova_Democracia.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T03-45-39-08-00-A_Nova_Democracia.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 03:45:39 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ORI/A Nova Democracia/Images/2024-03-27T03-45-39-08-00/000000.png"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[SP: In a meeting of women on 8/3, workers report town hall in popular condominium - the new democracy (A Nova Democracia)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Group of women Remís Carla held a meeting with the residents of the popular condominium Esplanada celebrating 08/03. At the time, they denounced the neglect of years and years by the City of Guarulhos and previous administrations to maintain the place.]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T03-56-28-08-00-A_Nova_Democracia.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T03-56-28-08-00-A_Nova_Democracia.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 03:56:28 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ORI/A Nova Democracia/Images/2024-03-27T03-56-28-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Mexico: bureaucratic capitalism using the example of the Interocean Corridor (Dem Volke Dienen)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Internet platform for the development of a revolutionary movement]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T04-05-50-08-00-Dem_Volke_Dienen.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T04-05-50-08-00-Dem_Volke_Dienen.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 04:05:50 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/Title.png"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Bolsonaro and military personnel are not interested in revealing who is the mentor of Marielle's murder - the new democracy (A Nova Democracia)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[While ideological and political mentors are not properly discovered, there is no basis for stating that the case was closed]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T05-11-18-08-00-A_Nova_Democracia.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T05-11-18-08-00-A_Nova_Democracia.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 05:11:18 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ORI/A Nova Democracia/Images/2024-03-27T05-11-18-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Unwavering Solidarity with Palestine – The Red Herald (Red Herald)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[oday it has been reported by the Gaza Health Ministry, that 32,414 Palestinians have been killed, and 74,787 wounded in Israel’s ongoing genocide in Gaza. We continuously report on the war.]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T06-44-00-08-00-Red_Herald.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T06-44-00-08-00-Red_Herald.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 06:44:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ORI/Red Herald/Images/2024-03-27T06-44-00-08-00/000000.png"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[France: Great images of the demonstration for the Paris Commune – The Red Herald (Red Herald)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Last Saturday, March 23rd, there was a demonstration in Saint Étienne, France, to celebrate the anniversary of the Paris Commune.]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T06-56-00-08-00-Red_Herald.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T06-56-00-08-00-Red_Herald.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 06:56:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ORI/Red Herald/Images/2024-03-27T06-56-00-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[25 years of the NATO-attack against Yugoslavia – The Red Herald (Red Herald)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[We publish this unofficial translation of an article of Rote Fahne.]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T07-06-00-08-00-Red_Herald.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T07-06-00-08-00-Red_Herald.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 07:06:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ORI/Red Herald/Images/2024-03-27T07-06-00-08-00/000000.png"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PC 27 March - Many American military vehicles are landing in Italy - denunciation of the ports of the autonomous collective of the port workers (Calp) of Genoa (proletari comunisti)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The autonomous collective of the port workers (Calp) of Genoa has denounced a new landing of military vehicles in the Ligurian port, arrives ...]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T14-00-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T14-00-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 14:00:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/Title.png"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[XANTHI An open discussion of racing moves - the race must continue, the law can be overthrown! (Resistance in the neighbourhood)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T14-28-00-08-00-Resistance_in_the_neighbourhood.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T14-28-00-08-00-Resistance_in_the_neighbourhood.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 14:28:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ORI/Resistance in the neighbourhood/Images/2024-03-27T14-28-00-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Teacher Racing Movements Illusions ended (Resistance in the neighbourhood)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T15-35-00-08-00-Resistance_in_the_neighbourhood.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T15-35-00-08-00-Resistance_in_the_neighbourhood.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 15:35:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ORI/Resistance in the neighbourhood/Images/2024-03-27T15-35-00-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[UB: The peasants took the wells back from a large farm after hitting the gunmen in a clash (Punalippu)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[We will publish a new Brazil websitearticle.Approximately 100 farmers organized by the Poor Peasant Association Jaqueira (Pernambuco) from various communities took back their wells, which had been fenced by a large farm company.March 18, about 100 LCP holders in Jaqueira, Pernambuco (PE) communities (Barro Branco, Furnas, Cabugi, Monteir, Caiana, Morcego, Caixa d'Andua, Tenório and Sítio Grande) combined their forces A large farm company Agropecuária Mata Sul S/A, owned by the farm of the farm Guilherme Maranhão.Since 2015, when the robbery of countries and wells began, the peasants have lived and produced the former Frei Caneca farm on land. Former Governor, Maranhão, supported by former governor Paulo Camara, made the gun groups threaten the entire population to expand cattle breeding to international exports through the Masterbory of the slaughterhouse.Despite comprehensive evidence of water poisoning with the pest of the water (in addition to the contamination of cattle stool), the Pernambuco Public Ministry (MPPE) and the Pernambuco Environmental Secretariat (CPRH) never began any criminal investigation company Agropecuária Mata Sul S/A.Thus, at the People's Assembly, the peasants decided to implement a large act to take the wells back from the large farm. The invitation reached the entire local population in flying markets and in all peasant communities affected by this environmental crime and against the health of the people. The peasants also organized joint efforts to clean and isolated the wells, 50 meters from the Large Lord's livestock farms and eucalyptus plantations.To do all this work, the status advocates dropped José Ricardo's revolutionary area of peasants and young students in the Mangue Vermelho movement. They helped to clear the bushes and mark the fences to protect the wells in the scorching sun. More, they met alongside the rest of the people, fighting the provocations of the gentlemen.As soon as the peasants had completed their joint effort with the first well in the first well of the day, singing folk songs and shouting slogans, half -time rifle from large farms appeared with tractors, stage farms, motorcycles and quads. The gunmen arrived with the posts, thread and eucalyptus seeds to put them in the same area that the peasants had just cleared. When the peasant march faced bands, representatives of the farmland began to threaten the peasants with firearms. The voltage led to a confrontation, three guns were injured, and the droon of the big farm was destroyed by the furious folk of firearms.This same March 18: A MPPE agricultural promoter, CPRH agents, representatives of the State Committee to monitor agrarian conflicts (CEACA), representatives of the pasture commission (CPT) and Pernambuco workers and peasant federation (Fetape) perhaps A large farming company Agropecuária from Mata Sul S/A visited to study complaints of the peasants made by the farm. According to this information, this Commission did not visit the peasant wells, but only to the places shown in the farm.However, the powerful action of the peasants forced the entire Commission to introduce the act at the scene of the Aktio and to approve two lawyers of the Brazilian Association of Folk Alliance (Abrapo) and the Commission of the Barro Branco Farm Association, and also had to accept the urgent conditions of the people in the public.Eventually, Mppe approved the proposal of the peasants represented by Abrapo to create a "water corridor" to separate the wells of the people. The status of the farm was ordered to pay the poles and the thread, the city administration sends employees and it was the responsibility of the State Environmental Department to investigate people's waters to determine pollution and to open a criminal investigation against the farm.After hearing the court, Guilherme Maranhão's gunmen asked for reinforcements from the Pernambuco Military Police (PM-PE) to plant eucalyptus for one of the wells that the peasants had been cleaned in cooperation, and Eduardo Figueredo, a lawyer of farm lords, declared that they would complete the militaryTwo vehicles were sent to bring security to the gunmen to continue their anti -folk action. This is not a courage to show, but rather a cowardice in front of a small display of peasants connected and organized by the agrarian revolution. It also demonstrates how dedicated the military forces of this old state are about protecting the interests of the state of space and promoting the poverty of the poor in the country and in the city.The peasants occupying the former Frei Caneca status are determined to take back all their wells and their land from the hands of the farm. In this way, they invite all peasants in the southern forest area of the Pernambuco to rise against the gunfire groups of large farms and the armed forces of this old state. Without destruction, large farms can never be entitled to the poor of the rural rural.Translated from the And's news:https://anovademocracia.com.br/pe-camponeses-retomam-fontes-dagua-do-latifundio-apos-derrotar-pistoleiros-em-confronto/]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T17-40-00-08-00-Punalippu.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T17-40-00-08-00-Punalippu.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 17:40:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ORI/Punalippu/Images/2024-03-27T17-40-00-08-00/000000.png"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Pirkanmaa: Posters and stickers in Valkeakoski (Punalippu)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[We publish the pictures sent to us by our readers. The photos were taken of posters and stickers in the city of Valkekoski, near Tampere. Valkeakoski is an industrial city that has traditionally been strong supporting the labor movement, which is reflected, for example, in the events of the 1918 Finnish Workers' Revolution. At that time, hundreds of the best boys and daughters in the city's working class were murdered by white bays.]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T18-00-00-08-00-Punalippu.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T18-00-00-08-00-Punalippu.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 18:00:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ORI/Punalippu/Images/2024-03-27T18-00-00-08-00/000000.png"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PC 27 March - Palestine continue the mobilizations in Milan, while other squares are added (proletari comunisti)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[After Friday at Cabi-Cattaneo, death factory in death and part of the Italian industrial military apparatus where the ...]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T18-47-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T18-47-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 18:47:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ORI/proletari comunisti/Images/2024-03-27T18-47-00-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PC March 27 - Stellantis: redundancies and "voluntary exits", the confederal unions sign (except Fiom) (proletari comunisti)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[“2,510 redundancies. Turin 1.560, Cassino 850 (of which 300 away from Pomigliano) and Pratola Serra 100 Esuberi "thus reports a note ...]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T19-35-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T19-35-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 19:35:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ORI/proletari comunisti/Images/2024-03-27T19-35-00-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Next initiatives of the unitary campaign for the release of Georges Abdallah (Association New Democracy)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[Subject: Next initiatives of the unitary campaign for the release of Georges Abdallah Good evening comrade, this message to inform you ...]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T22-36-00-08-00-Association_New_Democracy.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T22-36-00-08-00-Association_New_Democracy.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 22:36:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ORI/Association New Democracy/Images/2024-03-27T22-36-00-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PC March 27 - Turin Students in Fight - Stop of United to collaborations with Israeli universities! (proletari comunisti)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[the police loaded]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T23-34-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T23-34-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 23:34:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ORI/proletari comunisti/Images/2024-03-27T23-34-00-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PC 27 March - Also in Genoa, students' raid in the academic Senate against the agreements with Israel (proletari comunisti)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[A part of the demonstrators broke through the door and interrupted the meeting ...]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T23-41-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T23-41-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 23:41:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ORI/proletari comunisti/Images/2024-03-27T23-41-00-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[PC March 27 - Towards the imperialist war: governments want to reintroduce the objective lever (proletari comunisti)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[European countries should reintroduce mandatory military service and increase defense expenditure by bringing it back to ...]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T23-47-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-27T23-47-00-08-00-proletari_comunisti.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 23:47:00 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ORI/proletari comunisti/Images/2024-03-27T23-47-00-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Let's put the theater at the service of the town | Cultural Revolution (Revolucion Obrera)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[In Colombia, there are much that from their office as actors, directors and playwrights have been restless, worried and dedicated to telling the stories that]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-28T03-02-27-08-00-Revolucion_Obrera.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-28T03-02-27-08-00-Revolucion_Obrera.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 03:02:27 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ORI/Revolucion Obrera/Images/2024-03-28T03-02-27-08-00/000000.jpeg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Even in the midst of the siege against Bolsonaro and the military, STF assessment does not grow - the new democracy (A Nova Democracia)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[It is false that only Bolsonarist fanatics are right to criticize the Supreme Court. It is a mistake to leave to the far right the priority in the criticism of this oligarchic and anti-povo institution.]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-28T03-21-05-08-00-A_Nova_Democracia.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-28T03-21-05-08-00-A_Nova_Democracia.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 03:21:05 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ORI/A Nova Democracia/Images/2024-03-28T03-21-05-08-00/000000.png"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Augusto Heleno was spied on a structure set up by Jair Bolsonaro - the new democracy (A Nova Democracia)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The spy network that was structured by former President Jair Bolsonaro from the Israeli program “First Mile” was used to spy on Augusto Heleno. According to the Federal Police investigation, a mobile number used by Heleno for work issues was consulted 11 times, according to journalist Renata Agostini of the press monopoly O Globo.]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-28T04-40-48-08-00-A_Nova_Democracia.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-28T04-40-48-08-00-A_Nova_Democracia.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 04:40:48 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ORI/A Nova Democracia/Images/2024-03-28T04-40-48-08-00/000000.png"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Editorial - The question that does not want to silence: who had Marielle killed? - The new democracy (A Nova Democracia)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[The investigations, unlike the unfortunate speech of Luiz Inacio's minister, are not completed - at least, not from the scientific point of view and the truth. There is much to deepen if you want to prove the real motivation of the crime.]]></description>
            <link>https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-28T05-38-20-08-00-A_Nova_Democracia.htm</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ENG_NEW/HTMLs/2024-03-28T05-38-20-08-00-A_Nova_Democracia.htm</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 28 Mar 2024 05:38:20 +08:00</pubDate>
            <media:thumbnail width="240" height="135" url="https://ciangcing14.github.io/pages/2024-03-28/ORI/A Nova Democracia/Images/2024-03-28T05-38-20-08-00/000000.jpg"/>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
